<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>VGP Soylent Production</name>
	<targetVersion>1.0.0</targetVersion>
	<author>JuliaEllie  dismar  PhileasFogg</author>
	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=36926.msg378136#msg378136</url>
	<description>Adds Soylent Production...

(Does not require Vegetable Garden)

A more advance version of the mod.

- There aren't Soylent Cola and Soylent Medicine anymore. You can produce "Soylent Blue" (Animal Meat), "Soylent Purple" (Insect Meat), "Soylent Red" (Fruits  Vegetables) and "Soylent Yellow" (Animal Products) instead.
- You need to butcher the corpses (humans, insects and other animals) before you can "transfer" the meat into the corresponding "Soylent Type". So you will have some mood debuff.
- You can only process five pieces of ressource per action. So production time has been gone up quite a lot.
- Additionally "Soylent Products" aren't that OP anymore: one junk of meat / fruit / vegetable will be one piece of Soylent; Nutrition was reduced from 0.15 to 0.05.
- "Soylent Products" will rot eventually. But before they will last very long - even longer than pemmican (50% longer). And if you refrigate them, they will theoretically last forever.
- Research costs have been increased and electricity has been integrated as a research prerequesition.

But I also integrated some simplifications (and so raised the OPness of this mod):
- All "Soylent Products" will stack up to 500 items per tile.
- There is an additional research step: "Advanced Soylent Production". After researching that, you can mass produce all "Soylent Products" (100 pieces instead of five, at a 35% reduced production time). Also you will be able to produce "Survival Meals" out of "Soylent Products" and/or pemmican (at a higher ressource cost than regular "Survival Meal" production).


Orignal Mod made by master modder JuliaEllie. Maintain By dismar. Remastered by PhileasFogg!
https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=5450
	</description>
</ModMetaData>