<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>VGP Vegetable Garden</name>
  <author>dismarzero</author>
  <url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=36926.0</url>
  <targetVersion>1.0.0</targetVersion>
  <description>


Vegetable Garden 


Hello! And welcome to the new vegetable garden! 

Smaller pieces, easier to drop things you don't like, and enjoy more the things you like!


Vegetable Garden:

The main piece of my new project! Will have smaller bits of other mods built in. But tried keep the size down and still keep the spirit of the garden when used alone.

Tier Crop Growth:
Starter Crops
-potatoes - grows well anywhere
-corn - long growing with high yields
-rice - fast growing
-barley - immune to blight and used to make ale in the drinks mod. 

Tier 1 research "special property plants"
-snow beats - grows well anywhere, does not die from cold snaps
-lentils - meat substitute
-beans - many uses in the gourmet garden
-Olives - does not destroy plant when harvest, yield after first is faster

Tier 2 research fruits
-watermelon, grapes, blueberries, strawberries, agave

Tier 3 research fruit trees
-Apples, Bananas, Oranges, Peaches

Wild plants:
-Apples, Cherries, Bananas, Coconuts, Dates, Figs, Pineapple, Cloudberries, Gooseberries. 
-Mushrooms are grown in the wild and in hydropnics Can be used as a meat substitute.


Ingredients Plants:
-Coffee and Tea

Wood:
-Bamboo fast growing wood
-ironwood very beautiful but not for fuel


Other Features:
-Growable Grass
-Silage Animal Feed
-Bulk Meals: Makes 4x Simple, Fine, Lavish, Kibble, and Pemmican.
-Stir-Fry and Stew Recipes with added meal effects.
-New Categories for stockpiles.
-Coffee, Tea, and Fruit Drinks
-Bio-Fuel: fuel for fueled tables.
-New art work for items by Spoon.
-New Flower: Plumeria
-New Tree: Ironwood 
-Hydroponic hay grass, ambrosia, and baby agarilux (cave mushroom).
-New Floors for bamboo, ironwood.
-Convert Bamboo to Wood at the stonecutting table.

Patches for the following mods:
Animal Feed Trough adds silage to the Trough.
Vanilla patches my bamboo and bio-fuel into work tables. And 
 </description>
</ModMetaData>



